好了  睁开眼吧
Okay, open them.
- 怎么了  - 我们买不起这个的
- What? - We can't afford this.
你在开玩笑吗  我们当然买得起
Are you kidding me? Yes, of course we could.
我把退伍津贴全花这上面了
I spent my combat pay on it.
我们可以做朋友
We can be friends.
我有些朋友都四十好几了
Some of my best friends
还跟二十出头的年轻人约会
are 40-year-old guys who date 20-year-olds.
- 真的吗  - 当然不是  卡尔
- Really? - No, Carl, not really.
我现在想知道什么
Anything I need to know about?
你就得毫无保留地告诉我
You got to tell me this now.
我这儿没有你想知道的那档子事儿
There is nothing you need to know about.
我为你感到非常惋惜  好吗
I feel sorry for you, okay?
你为我感到惋惜  为什么
You feel sorry for me?Why?
你的那个儿子  对你来说就是个拖油瓶
That kid of yours,he's a retard.
现在究竟是个什么状况
What is going on right now?
我们俩都是成年人了  现在我们要去喝酒了
We're too adults,here,and now we're having a drink.
她才十九，而你比她整整大了九岁
She's 19.You're 28.
我现在对你们感到非常失望
I'm extremely disappointed right now.
我们得讨论一下让他留级的事儿
We need to discuss getting him back into fourth grade.
我们不会那样做的
We're not doing that.
你要是不喜欢这样的话  就跟艾德说去
You don't like it, talk to ed.
我的艺术班要去意大利一个月
My art class is going to Italy for a month.
我要去
I'm gonna go.
独自一人去
By myself.
早上好  贝克里
Good morning, Berkeley!
嗯
Mm.
再有你就更好了
You'd better.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
拿到你了
There we go.
好了
All right.
? 乐队奏响了“致元首的欢呼”?
? And then the band plays"hail to the chief" ?
感觉不错
Oh, yeah.
? 绝对不是我  绝对不是我 ?
? It ain't me, it ain't me ?
哦  一杆进洞
Whoo, that's in the hole!
太棒了
Oh, yeah!
?我绝非幸运的家伙?
? I ain't no fortunate one ?
气色不错嘛  奇克
Looking good, Zeek.
嗨  谢莉
Hi, Shelly!
糟了
Gah.
看起来你的思绪整理的不错嘛
So, uh, looks like you made up your mind.
你要去跳芭蕾而不是打篮球了
You gonna do ballet instead of basketball?
对  我要跟老妈一起去跳芭蕾
Yup, I'm doing ballet with mom now.
劈叉不错
Hey, nice turn-out.
他看起来很棒对吧  亲爱的
Doesn't he look great, honey?
对啊
Yeah.
然后你只需要顺着
And then you just--we slide his pants
他自己的意愿  或者...
up on over those, or...
很棒
Okay.
伊万校长也要与会
Principal Evans is gonna be at the meeting too.
这可是件大事儿
This is a big deal.
很棒  那我们周五出去
Okay, so we'll go out on Friday.
去搞清楚他们到底要谈什么
We'll find out what it's about then.
我们知道他们要谈什么  就那档子事儿嘛
Well, we know what it's about.This is it.
他们要谈因为维克多跟不上进度
This is when they're telling us they're gonna hold him back
要让他留级的事儿
because he's not keeping up.
- 这可不一定  茱莉亚  - 他现在还在努力呢
- We don't know that,Julia.- He's really still struggling.
- 这可不一定  - 好吧
- We don't know that. - Oh, fine.
我只是太讨厌等待了
Well, I just hate waiting.
我知道  我都知道
I know you do.I know you do.
我不知道还能怎么做
I don't know what else I can do.
- 我是说  - 亲爱的
- I mean, - Honey.
我跟他一起努力了那么久
I've been working with him so much--
别这样  凡事儿都别往坏处想
Come on, let's not assume the worst, here
求你了  好吗
Please? Please?
我们都清楚他们要让他留级
We know that they're gonna hold him back.
维克多要重新去念四年级吗
Victor's going back to fourth grade?
- 不是  - 我说的可不是那样
- No. - That's not what I said.
是  你就是那样说的
Yes,it--that's exactly what you just said.
那样太糟了  我可不想跟他在同一班念书
That's awful.I don't want him in my class.
【全体七嘴八舌的在说话】
[All talking at once]
你需要穿上你的衣服还有拿上你的书
You need a jacket and your school books--
我已经都准备好我的东西了
I already have my stuff.
- 都准备好了   - 拜托
- It's packed up. - Come on.
你们想吃午饭吗
You guys want some lunch?
想吃什么都行  谁要
Anything? Anyone?
我这儿有几个选择：汉堡跟馅饼  意大利菜...
Now, I got some options:Burger and pie, Italian...
- 你总是那个跟我们喂食的人  - 还有两份墨西哥菜
- You're always feeding us. - Two Mexicans.
- 你们想吃什么  - 哇哦  哇哦  哇哦
- What do you guys want? - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 我们还有“冰淇淋”（喻指戒指）呢  - 住手  别这样
- We got ice cream. - Stop. Don't.
- 是真的吗  - 当然是真的
- Is that real? - Yeah, it's real.
- 这是真的  - 那真是真的
- It's real. It's--  - That's real?
- 对  - 公主方切的吗
- Yes. - Princess cut?
这可钻石成色并不是很高
It's the quality is not as high.
- 我们有颜色...  - 你们怎么回事啊
- We have color-- - What is your deal?
你们这样真是太奇怪了  能别这样了吗
You guys are such weirdos.Can we not do this?
- 好大一颗啊  - 别让贾思敏看到
- It's massive. - Do not show that to Jasmine.
- 亮瞎了我的钛合金狗眼  -嗯 很好
- Blinding my sight, here. - Yeah, it's good.
我们能...你们想吃什么
Can we--what do you guys want to eat?
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
我找你有事儿
It's the lady I was looking for.
哦  抱歉
Oh, oh, sorry, yeah.
干衣机现在还不能用
The dryer's still not working.
修理工几天晚些时候才能来
The guy is coming later today.
不  这个倒不急
No, it's not even close.
我周六晚上有个小型派对
I'm having a little party Saturday night and--
而你不希望我到时候叫警察来对吧
and you don't want me to call the cops.
事实上  我是想邀请你来着
I actually wanted to invite you.
没错  就是你
You.
- 给你   - 你在邀请我吗
- Here you go. - You're inviting me?
我想既然我们都共用一个浴花了  那么...
Well, you know,I feel like we shared a loofah, so...
嗯~ 我不知道
Um, I--I just--I'm not--I don't know
我周末会不会有事  但还是很感谢你
what my weekend is, uh, but thank you.
不客气  我觉得你会喜欢的
You're welcome.Yeah, I think you'd enjoy it.
- 你应该来的  - 哦
- You should come. - Oh.
就几个朋友和一些音乐而已
Just a few friends and music.
还有一点酒  会很有趣的
Drinks.It'll be fun.
还有其他二十六岁以上的人去吗
Anyone else over 26 gonna be there?
我希望没有  没有
I hope not, no.
嗯~
Mm.
- 待会儿见  - 开玩笑  开玩笑
- See you later. - Kidding. Kidding.
好吧  你还是该来的
Okay.You should come though.
会觉得它会很棒的
Think it'll be good.
我会打电话叫你出来吃饭  我们到时再...
I'll call you for dinner and we'll have--
好了  各位  听好了
all right, guys, listen up.
就说一小会儿
I just want to talk to you for a second.
最新的民意检测情况出炉了
So the new poll numbers came in
我只想说很感激你们
and I just want to say how much I appreciate
所有人在这场竞选上
all the hard work every last one of you
所投入的心血和汗水
have been putting into this campaign.
我是说  要是没有你们各位的努力
I mean, the passion--we wouldn't have even
我们不会走到这么远的
gotten this far without you guys--
海瑟   你说的很对
Heather, you're--you're so right.
你们各位都是非常努力的员工
You guys are such hard workers.
他们都有着良好的职业操守
They have such great work ethic.
- 我只想让你知道...  - 民意票数如何
- And I just want you to know...
- What are the poll numbers?
我们只比小鲍低两个百分点了
Well, we're within two points Bob little.
你没开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
- 真的吗  - 你知道这意味着什么吗
- I really am? - Do you know what this means?
- 你会赢的  我们就要成功了  - 我可以赢的
- You're gonna win.We're gonna do this.- Icould win.
- 两个百分点吗  - 俩百分点
- Two points? - Two points.
我们会把差距缩小为零  你曾经是输家
We're gonna close this gap.You were the underdog.
- 现在你却高他俩百分点  - 我是赢家
- Now you're two points away. - I'm the top dog.
她是赢家  在多用两周时间 各位
She's the top dog.Two more weeks, people.
- 两个百分点  - 你们知道这意味着什么吗
- Two points. - You know what this means?
你们得比之前更加努力的工作了
You guys have to work harder than ever.
我想让你们继续工作  哦  是Trib那边打来的
I want you to work. Oh, it's the trib.
他们可能想问民意检测的情况
They probably want a comment about the polls.
喂
Yeah, hello?
对 说吧
Yeah, talk to me.
啊~ 等等  什么
Uh, wait, what?
你从哪得知的  小鲍吗
Who'd you get that from?Bob little?
- 怎么了  - 有点在哪儿
- What? - Where's Adam?
打扰一下  你是亚当・布雷弗曼吗
Excuse me.Are you Adam Braverman?
对 我是
Yeah, I am.
请问你在超市对一位男士
Is it true that you violently assaulted
进行暴力攻击行为这是真的吗
a man in a supermarket?
什么
What?
你认为这些指控
How do you think these allegations
会影响你妻子的市长竞选吗
are gonna affect your wife's bid of mayor?
我...我不知道  你们能别拍...
I...I don't know.Would you please--
你曾经因愤怒管理问题接受过治疗吗
have you ever been treated for anger management issues?
布雷弗曼先生  我们有几个问题想问你
Mr. Braverman, we have questions.
没有  我没有  你们能从我家草地上离开吗
No, I have not.Would you just get off my lawn?
这可是私人财产
This is private property.
行吗  滚出我家的草地
All right?Get off my lawn?
快滚  天呐
Go! God!
? May God bless and keep you always
为人父母
? and may your wishes all come true
? may you always do for others
? and let others do for you
? may you build a ladder to the stars
? and climb on every rung
? and may you stay
? forever young
? may you grow up to be righteous
? may you grow up to be true
? may you always know the truth
? and see the lights surrounding you
? may you always be courageous
? stand upright and be strong
? and may you stay
? forever young
? may you stay
? forever young?
第五季第八集幕雨字幕组译制
翻译：Brynt&超威闫叔  校对：Brynt&超威闫叔
时间轴：花格子神尼&拜仁小攀  后期：Brynt
你在超市暴力袭击一位男士的事儿是真的吗
Is it true that you violently assaulted a man in a supermarket?
什么  什么  什么
What? What? What?
你认为这些指控会影响
How do you think these allegations
你妻子的市长竞选吗
are going to affect your wife in her bid for mayor?
滚出我的草地  我不知道
Get off my lawn!I don't know.
滚出我的草地  滚出我的草地
Get off my lawn!Get off my lawn!
亲爱的  事情真没那么糟糕
You know,honey,it's not really--it's not that bad.
我当时根本就没时间去想  就应激反应而已
I didn't have time to think.I just reacted.
- 显而易见  - 你什么也没说
- Obviously. - You didn't say anything.
还有  下次遇到这种事  你只需要说“无可奉告”
Well, next time, you should just say "no comment."
- 下一次吗  - 然后走开就行了
- Next time? - And walk away.
我希望没有下次了
I hope there's not a next time.
我都不知道为什么会有这次的状况
I don't even know why there had to be a this time.
这都是三年前的事了
This was, like,three years ago.
- 这就是他们的伎俩  - 那个家伙侮辱了我的孩子
- Well, this is what they did.- The guy insulted my kid.
- 他叫我儿子拖油瓶  我就揍了他  - 他确实该打
- He called him a retard.I punched him. - He did.
我又没把他打进医院  可谁又会关心这个呢
It's not like I put him in the hospital. Who cares?
你当时做的很对  你做的非常对
You were right to do that.You were,you're right.
我非常高兴当时审查过你了  亚当
I'm glad I vetted you too,Adam.
我非常高兴在你办公室待了俩小时
I'm glad I spent those two hours in your office
你告诉我你跟
and you telling me about streaking
一对母女一起拍裸照的事儿
at a mother-daughter banquet and you were naked.
这高兴你么诶跟我说这件事
Glad you forgot to tell me about this.
- 在哪儿拍的  - 当时我和还在上高中
- Where? - When I was in High School.
- 你知道这件事的  - 真的吗
-  You know about this. - Really?
- 你们俩有听我说话吗  - 抱歉
- Are you guys paying attention? - Sorry.
我再说小鲍发现了一个能削弱你竞争力的方法
I'm saying Bob little has found a way to go negative.
我们一落千丈了
We're down to the wire.
他会将这俩百分点的优势
He can turn this two point lead
变成五个百分点的
into a five point lead.
我们到时候就任人宰割了
We'll be cooked when he does that.
你说得对
You're right.
我不明白他是怎么挖出这件事的
Well, I don't understand how he found out about this.
- 我也不知道  - 我告诉他的
- I don't either. - I told him.
- 什么  - 我...几年前
- What? - I--years ago.
我当年还在为他工作的时候告诉他的
I told him when I was working for him.
他当时觉得你这样做
He thought it was so awesome and that you were the man
是非常酷的  也非常棒
and it was so cool and great.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我简直不敢相信那个小王八蛋
I can't believe that little bastard
能记起这件事还拿来攻击你
remembered this and tried to use it against you.
我懂了  你知道我们现在该怎么做吗
Yes, I get it.You know what we should do?
- 我们去召开一个记者发布会  - 不 不行
- Let's call a press conference. - No, no.
我们不需要再给他们更多答复
We don't need to give this more play.
我们需要消极手段了  这才是我们该做的
We need to go negative.That's what we need to do.
我们需要去挖掘一些“清白”先生的故事了
We need to find some story about mister squeaky clean.
然后再走露出去
Mr. little and leak that out.
- 他绝对不会是清白的  - 我知道他不是
- Oh, he's not squeaky clean. - I know he's not.
我已经厌倦了那种形象了
I'm tired of that image anyway.
我们得挖出一点猛料了
There's got to be something we could dig up on him.
- 你知道什么吗  你发现过...  - 我没有...
-You know anything?Anything you found out..-I don't..
当你帮他竞选的时候  有出过什么事吗
When you were running his campaign,anything come up?
一定会有什么事的  我得去挖出来
There's got to be something.I'm gonna find it.
- 我爱你  - 今天过得怎么样
- I love you. - How was your day?
- 好吧  我累死了  - 是吗
- Okay. I'm tired. - Yeah?
我们在录一首新歌
Yeah, we just started recording a new track
而我觉得...我也说不清楚
and I'm just, like...I don't know.
我感觉像是被榨干了一样
I feel really drained.
有谁注意到你有所不同了吗
Anybody notice anything,uh,different about you?
- 当然啦  - 那他们有何评价
- Yes, of course. - What'd they say?
- 他们怎么可能不评头论足嘛  - 他们有没有惊呆了
- How could they not? - Did they freak out?
他们简直不敢相信  对  他们...
They couldn't believe it.Yeah, they--
- 那他们兴奋吗  - 非常兴奋
- Were they excited? - Very excited.
他们觉得戒指非常赞
They thought it was amazing.
克罗斯比还说“千万别告诉贾思敏”
Yeah, Crosby said, you know,"don't show Jasmine that
“否则我就得加倍努力给她也买一个了”
or I'm gonna have to upgrade and get her one of those.
嗯  太糟了
Well, too bad.
这可是绝版的  所以她没机会了
It's one of a kind, so she can't...
- 这枚戒指吗  - 她没...对
- This? - She can't--yeah.
- 哇哦  - 看看它
- Wow. - Look at that.
这世上的唯一
Only one in the world.
我甚至都不...我甚至都不敢再给它加工了
I don't even--I can't even process it.
它跟你简直是绝配
It's just--it looks so perfect on you.
这太不可思议了
It's crazy.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
太让人难以置信了
It's--it's--it's unbelievable.
我去做晚饭
I'm gonna make us dinner.
好吧  迅雷
Okay.Thanks, then.
- 老爸  - 在呐
- Dad? - Yup.
- 哦  - 我在这儿呢
- Oh. - I'm in here.
快进来吧
Come on in.
太棒了
Oh, yeah.
- 你在干...  - 嗯~
- What are you-- - Mm.
天呐  我一直都想这么做来着
Man, I've always wanted to do that.
真的吗
Really?
我正在尝试不同的食物搭配
I'm experimenting with different food groups.
- 太美味了   - 那是什么
- Very good. - What is it?
谷质鲜奶油跟香蕉的结合体
It's cereal with whipped cream and a banana.
- 老爸  - 干嘛
- Dad. - What?
你最近都是这么吃的吗
Is this the way you've been eating?
呃  貌似是吧  好吧 就是这样吃的
Uh, kind of, yeah.
你们这帮孩子怎么总时不时跑过来
Why do the kids keep stopping by here
是来视察我的现状吗
and then, like, checking on me?
你们不需要来视察我
You don't need to check on me.
- 我一个人也会活得好好的  - 老爸  我就搞不懂了
- I'm gonna be fine. - Well, dad, I don't know.
你都一个人生活了那么久了
It's been a long time since you've been on your own
所以我才跑过来看看你的
and, you know, so I was next in the rotation..
你也一个人生活那么久了
Well,it's been a long time since you've been on your own.
你的孩子有来视察过你吗
Do the kids keep checking up on you?
- 别人有没有时不时跑来逗留呢  - 没有 老爸
- Do people stop by? - No, dad.
他们也不会提着这个包袱过来
And they don't bring me what's in this bag either,
- 所以我想我还是走吧   - 别 别  别
- so I guess I'll just go--  - No, no, no.
等等  等等
Wait a minute.Hold it.
- 嗯   - 回来
- Hm? - Get back here.
你包里装的什么
What's in the bag?
- 你想知道吗  - 嗯
- Do you want to know? - Uh-huh.
这包里的土豆沙拉
Well, the potato salad is in the bag
你只能在旧金山才买得到
that you can only get in San Francisco,
更不用说我为什么大老远从旧金山
which is why I came from San Francisco
跑过来拿给你了
to give it to you,not to mention...
- 哇哦  - 对
- Ooh. - Yeah.
这排骨都还是热的呢   烫烫烫
The ribs that are hot,hot, hot, hot, hot.
哦~ 让我闻闻  快让我闻闻
Oh, let me smell them.Let me smell.
嗯~~
Mm.
因为我非常爱您  我还给你特别带了酱料
And because I love you,I got you extra sauce.
哦  还有酱料
Oh, the extra sauce.
我们现在就吃  行吗
Let's eat it now, shall we?
- 好吧  行  - 太好了
- Okay, yeah. - Okay.
- 我也想试试这个  - 哦  轻点喷
- I want to try this though. - Oh, easy.
- 真恶心   - 对啊
- Ew. - Yeah.
那天的芭蕾舞课程上的如何了
So, hey, how was ballet class the other day?
- 非常棒  - 是吗
- Um, it was good. - It was?
非常非常棒
Yeah, it was actually really good.
- 真的很棒啊   - 对
- Oh, it was really good. - Yeah.
那你最喜欢这课哪一点
What's the thing you like best about it?
我喜欢从外婆房顶上把小妹给扔下去
I like when we drop the baby off at grandma's house.
嗯   她可不算个舞者
Yeah, she's not much of a dancer.
她更像是个流口水的家伙
She's more of a drooler really, huh?
- 对啊  - 你还喜欢什么
- Yeah. - What else you like about it?
哦
Ooh!
老妈跟我之后还吃了汉堡跟馅饼
Mom and I get to have burger and pie after.
她让我随便点我想吃的东西
She lets me order whatever I want
因为她说芭蕾是个非常棒的运动
because ballet's such a good exercise.
嗯
Mm.
要有汉堡跟馅饼的话  我也去跳芭蕾
Yeah, I'd even do ballet for burger and pie.
你得朝前看了
You have to move forward.
- 好吧  - 这就对了
- Oh, okay. - There you go.
小鬼  你要是只是为了吃汉堡跟馅饼
You know, buddy,if you're just doing ballet
才去跳芭蕾的话
so you can spend time with mom and eat at burger and pie
我会帮你保密的
I won't tell her.
我只是好奇是不是...
You know, I'm just curious if that's...
不  老爸  我真的很喜欢跳芭蕾
No, dad.I really like ballet.
- 真的吗  - 真的
- Really? - Yeah.
其实我觉得我爱上跳芭蕾了
Actually, I think I love it.
- 砰  - 你爱跳芭蕾吗
- Boom! - You love it?
你喜欢...下蹲吗
Do your--do, like, a plie.
- 做你的...  - 下蹲吗  怎么蹲
- Do your--  - Do a plie? What?
就像这样
Yeah, like this.
这样有用吗
How is that gonna help?
我懂了  再低点
I got you.Oh, lower.
- 转移你的重心  - 嗯
- Move your center of gravity. - Yeah.
我告诉过你这会奏效的
I told you it's perfect.
这真是...它们真就这样长起来了诶
This is--yeah,they're really coming along.
那肥料真是神奇啊
Incredible with that fertilizer.
- 不好意思   明基朵老师  - 哦  嗨
- Excuse me, Miss Mikindoe. - Oh, hi.
嗨
Hi.
我知道我们周五才能面谈
I know we have a meeting on the books for Friday
你肯定也不希望在校外跟我谈
and you probably don't want to speak out of school but--
- 我真的不能现在跟你聊  - 哦
- well, no, I can't. - Oh.
我是说  周五这个时间很好
I mean,Friday is the best time.
伊万校长也能来
Principal Evans will be there.
对  我知道  我知道
Right.I know, I know.
要是你能给我个
If you could give me anything--
就一点小小的提示...
just a little heads up on...
- 我真的不能  - 好吧
- I really can't. - Okay.
- 好吧  - 哦...
- Okay. - Oh--
我现在都为这事儿夜不能寐了
I can't sleep.
我...
I'm...
不知道我儿子到底发生了什么事
I'm really having a rough time
让我日子真不好过
not knowing what's happening with my son.
我现在成天都想着这事儿  所以...
It's kind of all I'm thinking about, so, um...
这件是真的该由校长亲口来说的
This really should come from the principal.
什么  到底是什么事
What?Well, what is it?
我知道你一直都很努力
Well, I know you've been working really hard
但是他现在真是越来越落后了
and he just keeps falling more and more behind.
好吧
Right.
我们不想让他
We don't want himto fall anymore behind
再继续落后下去了
than he already is.
- 嗯  - 我们想让他成功
- Right. - We want him to succeed.
好吧  那...
Right.So...
所以我们建议让他
So we're recommending that he move back
今年余下的时间会四年级去念书
to the fourth grade for the rest of the year.
- 好吧  - 我很抱歉
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
- 我真的很抱歉  - 不
- I'm really sorry. - No.
我知道这样做有多难
I know how hard this is gonna be.
我很抱歉  我本不该跟你说这些的
I'm sorry.I shouldn't have said anything.
我应该等到跟校长见了面再跟你说的
I should have waited until we were with the principal.
我很感激你能告诉我这些
Oh, I really appreciate you telling me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 一切都会好起来的  - 好吧
- It's gonna be okay. - Okay.
好了  我们周五再见
All right, I'll see you Friday.
- 好吧  - 好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
拜
Bye.
我知道我什么都搞砸过
So I know I suck at pretty much everything,
但幸好这个南瓜没有
but apparently not squash.
茱莉亚  怎么啦
Julia, what's wrong?
你还好吗  出什么事了
Are you okay? What happened?
嗯
Mm.
天呐
Oh, God.
他们终于还是要让维克多留级到四年级
They're finally moving Victor back to fourth grade now.
我现在不知道怎么办了
And...I don't know.
天呐  我很遗憾 真的很遗憾
God, I'm sorry, Julia. I am.
我都不知道要怎么告诉他了
I don't know how to tell him.
天呐
Oh, God.
我要...
I'm gonna...
我要跟我老公讲这事儿
Um, go talk to my husband.
- 嗯  - 好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
- 谢谢你   - 你真还好吗
- Thank you. - You okay?
嗯  我还好
Okay, yeah. I'm okay.
- 嘿  布伦达  最近如何  - 嘿  克里斯蒂娜
- Hey, Brenda. How are you? - Hey, Kristina.
- 嘿  你还好吗  - 对了  他现在在打电话
- Hey, how are you doing?- Oh, he's on a call right now.
没关系  我就耽搁他几分钟
Oh, it's okay.It'll just take a second.
- 你不能进去  克里斯蒂娜  - 就几分钟时间
- You can't go in thereChristina.- Just one quick second.
没事的  没什么大事儿
It's fine.It's really no big deal.
- 就耽搁一会儿  - 克里斯蒂娜  你好吗
- It'll be two seconds.- Kristina! How are you?
我好得不得了  鲍勃  你呢
I'm great, Bob.How are you?
- 想来杯咖啡吗  - 不想
- You want a coffee?- No, I don't want a coffee.
我什么都不想喝  听着
I don't want anything.Listen to me.
我想让你承认
I just want you to tell me straight
亚当那件事是你捅出去的  别拐弯抹角
that this story about Adam came from you.
- 我知道是你干的  - 别这样
- I know that it did. - Come on.
我简直不敢相信你会做出这种事
I can't believe that you would do this.
我本以为我们俩是朋友
I mean,I thought we were friends.
我对你干什么事儿了  你就不敢相信
You can't believe I would do what to you?
这完全是对我们俩友谊的背叛
This is a complete betrayal of our friendship
背叛  等等  克里斯蒂娜
Betrayal?Kristina, hold on a second.
不要  我才不要等等  我现在非常愤怒
No, I'm not gonna hold on.I'm actually pissed.
竞选本来就有点污秽不堪
Campaigns get a little messy,Kristina.
我都懂  我知道
I get it.I know that.
要是你知道的话  那还为什么要跑到这儿来大吼大叫
Well, if you know that,then why are you here yelling--
我才是那个竞选的人  不是我的家人
I'm the one running,Bob, not my family.
- 这我完全理解  - 别把他们给卷进来  行吗
- I completely understand that.
- Leave them out of it,okay?
你听懂了吗  你知道什么吗
Do you get that?You know what,
我手上一样也有你不为人知的事儿
there are some things that I could share
别逼我告诉公众  你...
about you, Bob, that...
继续说啊  克里斯蒂娜
Go ahead, Kristina.
但是你根本就不会说什么
But you're not gonna say anything
因为你根本就不是那样的人
'cause that's just not who you are.
否则的话  我两年前也就会赢得那场选举
Otherwise,I would have won that campaign two years ago.
但这次我绝对不会输
But I'm not gonna lose this one.
你一点都不了解我的为人
You don't know who I am.
一点都不
No idea.
Not a clue.
你真该去看看他当时的那副嘴脸
You should have seen the little look on his face.
- 他对着我得意的笑  我真想当时就...  - 我知道
- He was smirking at me.I want to,like..- I know.
冲上去狠狠揍他一顿
I wanted to punch him.
他知道我不会对他使阴招
He knows that I can't go negative on this.
他在跟你玩心理战呢
He's playing mind games with you.
他在跟我玩心理战
He's playing mind games with me.
你得证明他错了  好吗
You got to prove him wrong,okay?
我该怎么做才能证明他错了
How am I gonna prove him wrong?
在不提及安博的情况下给他狠狠一击
With the way doing it without mentioning Amber's name.
- 那要怎么做  亲爱的  - 小鲍
- How, honey?- Bob little.
跟实习生乱搞关系  就这样就行
Inappropriate behavior with an intern and that's it.
我不想把安博给卷进来
I don't want to bring Amber into this.
- 这件事太私人了  - 我们不会把安博给卷进来的
- It's like--it's too personal.
- We won't bring Amber into this.
她是我的家人  是我的侄女
She's family.She's my niece.
我觉得应该让海瑟来衡量这件事儿
I think that we should have Heather weigh in on this.
我绝对不会跟海瑟说这件事儿
I am not checking with Heather.
我要是我告诉她安博跟鲍勃的事  就什么都完蛋了
If I tell her about Amber and Bob, it's over.
你已经见识过她得厉害了  不是吗
You've met her, okay?
她一定会直击要害
She'll go right for the jugular--
我不想成为导致你竞选事业结束的引子
I just don't want to be the reason this ends for you.
我不会输的
I'm not going to lose.
我绝对不会输的
I'm not losing.
我就喜欢你被激怒的样子
I love it when you get feisty like that.
- 我没有被激怒好吗  我只是有点生气而已  - 那只是...
- I'm not feisty.I'm just mad.- The one that just--
我要下楼去处理这件事儿了
I'm going downstairs to fix this.
你决定怎么做了吗
What'd you decide?
亲爱的
Honey?
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 看到你的留言了  - 我帮你接收红酒包裹
- Got you note.- I got your wine delivery.
谢谢
Thank you.
这酒据说非常赞的
This is supposed to be an amazing label.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
他们告诉我的是这是非常香的果酒
I'm told it's fruit-forward with a very big nose.
- 对我来说什么酒都一样  - 你要来吗
- It's all the same to me. - You coming?
我嘛...
Oh, I--you know...
你是房客  而我是你的房东  我不...
You're the tenant.I'm your super. I don't...
我知道你认为这会是
I know you think it's gonna be, you know,
一帮二十多岁的年轻人的狂欢
me and a bunch of 20-something's doing shooters,
但我确实还是有一些三十多的朋友来参加
but I do have some friends in their 30s.
四十多岁的都有呢
Even their 40s.
不许告诉别人
Don't tell anybody.
谢了  但我家里确实还有点事儿
Thanks, but I have a family thing.
好吧  谢谢你帮我拿包裹
Okay.Thanks for hanging onto it.
应该的
Sure.
对了  萨拉
Hey, Sarah?
管它那么多呢
You know,for what it's worth...
就算你周六的派对不想来
Even if you don't want to come to my party Saturday,
你还是应该去参加别的派对的
you should go to a party.
像你这个年纪的女人周六晚上就该出去玩
Yeah,a woman like you should be out on Saturday night.
我认为大家都觉得暴力手段
Well,I think we can all agree that resorting to violence
不是正确的家庭价值观
is not a family value.
真正的家庭价值观应该是...
I think this is really about moving...
- 天呐  我怎么就没想到呢  - 出什么事儿了
- Boy, have I seen it.- What's happening?
我就是觉得这种行径太恶心了  你知道吗
I am just disgusted.You know what?
我简直不敢相信他会做出这种事
I can't believe that he would do this.
安博  我也不敢相信  我只是...
Amber, I can't either.I'm just--
我现在都快愁死了  你知道吗
I'm so bummed, you know?
我觉得好像...
Like, I feel like...
我还以为他怎么都还是个不错的家伙
I thought he was,like, a good guy generally.
我们曾经是朋友啊  我们是朋友啊
We were friends, you know? We're friends.
我现在觉得好像被背叛了一样
I just feel, like,totally betrayed and...
- 这样太糟了  - 我已经厌倦了
- It's so awful.- I'm just tired and...
- 我也说不清楚  - 你知道我们该怎么做
- I don't know.- You know what we have to do.
我...
I...
- 你敢  - 你必须这样做
- Don't you dare. - You have to.
- 好吗  - 你知道我们别无他法
- Okay? - You know that there's no way--
你亚当舅舅已经跟我谈过这件事儿了
Uncle Adam and I have been talking about this
他一直在问我...
and he's been asking--
- 很好  很好呀  - 一点都不好
- Good. Good. - No, it's not good.
- 我不想把你卷进来  - 没关系的
- I'm not pulling you into this. - It doesn't matter.
我们在有这件把柄的时候
There's no way that we can let him get away with this--
绝对不能让他就这么侥幸逃脱
with spinning something like what Uncle did
他对亚当舅舅的所作所为
into this when we have this on him.
- 我知道我们有这件把柄 但是 - 这样做一点都没错
- I know we have it, but, honey,
- It's the right thing to do.
你也会暴露在媒体之下的
you would be all over the media.
- 不管你是在工作还是回家 还是做其他事 - 没关系的
- They would be following you.- That's fine.
-  他们都会一直跟着你的- 我自会处理的
- To work, home, everything.- I can handle it.
我不想这种家伙当选
I don't want this guy in office.
- 我知道  -他太不诚信了
- I know. - He's dishonest.
我也不想  我会好好考虑这件事的
I don't either,but I'll think about it.
你答应我你真会考虑
Do you promise you'll think about it for real?
我发誓  我向你保证
I swear I will.I promise.
- 你保证  - 我们拉钩为誓
- Do you promise. - I pinkie promise...
- 拉钩  - 我会好好考虑的
- Pinkie promise. - That I'll think about it.
等...等等
What--wait.
- 那是什么  - 你还没见过吗
- What is that? - You haven't seen it?
天呐  简直是
Oh, my God.That is, like--
我看不见了  亲爱的  这真是太棒了
I can't see.Honey, that is so pretty.
- 嗯  对  - 太浪漫了
- Yeah, it's--yeah. - Oh, how sweet.
- 哦~~  -对啊
- Oh. - Yeah.
你不喜欢吗
You don't really love it?
有点荒唐  对吧
It's a little bit absurd,right?
不只是我
It's not just me?
我是说  它比我们家任何一个人
I mean, it's bigger than any
的婚戒都还要大
of my family members wedding rings, I mean--
确实是比我的要大些  但是...
well, it's a little bigger than mine, but...
我们到底在干嘛呢
Like,what are we doing?
- 好好享受它吧  好吗  - 我不需要这个
- Enjoy it, you know? - I don't need it.
他把他所有的钱都花上面了
And he spent all of his money on it.
倾家荡产了都
Everything that he had.
你们俩就要结婚了  你知道吗
You guys are gonna be married.You know what?
跟他谈谈  告诉他
Have this talk with him and tell him
你在担心财政问题  而且可能...
that you're worried about finances and maybe just...
- 我很害怕呀  - 告诉他就对了
- I'm just scared. - Just tell him.
我怕伤了他的心
I don't want to hurt his feelings.
我觉得他会非常沮丧的
I feel like he's gonna get upset.
你确定只是因为这戒指的事儿
Are you sure it's just about the ring?
- 对  - 好吧
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
对  我们一切都还好  我只是... 还好
Yeah, everything's fine.I just... Yeah.
很好
Good.
好了  他们都在做家庭作业了
Okay, they're both doing homework.
- 好吧  - 好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
我说对了  他们要让他留级了
I was right.They're gonna hold him back.
你从哪知道...
And you know this...
我今天偶遇到明基朵老师了  她跟我说的
I ran into Miss Mikindoe today at school and she told me.
- 偶遇吗  - 所以 ...对
- Ran into? - So... Yeah.
我在那弄责任委员会的事儿
I was there for sustainability.
所以你就情不自禁了
And you just couldn't help yourself.
乔
Joel.
我是说  你就不能打电话给我
I mean, you can't call me about this,
- 或是给我发短信给我说要讨论一下...- 你之前在工作诶
- or text me have a discussion-- - You were at work.
而且我现在在告诉你啊
And I'm telling you now.
所以你就一个人跑去找明基朵老师
So you went and had our conversation
讨论我们要一起讨论的话题
with Miss Mikindoe without me.
我是偶遇到她的  我们能讨论正事儿吗
I ran into her and can we talk about the real issue, here?
我们儿子在学年中途的时候
Our son is being yanked out of his class
被赶出原来的班了诶
in the middle of the school year
我们得相处怎样去告诉他这件事儿
and we need to figure out how to talk to him about it.
不行  我们不会那样做的
No.We are not doing that.
我觉得我们别无选择
I don't think we have a choice.
我们有  茱莉亚
Yes, we do, Julia.
我们要去告诉校长
We're gonna go in and tell the principal
他这样会毁了的
that he can go screw himself.
哦
Oh.
我们非得现在把他给弄出来吗
We're gonna pull out son out right now?
这对他来说是个灾难
It's gonna be a total disaster for him.
我知道
I know.
这就是我为什么想在学年开始的时候
That's why I wanted to do it
就让他留级
at the beginning of the school year.
哦  这都是我的错吗  都怪我是吗
Oh, so this is my fault?This is all on me?
- 不是  - 你不就是那样说的吗
- No. - Is that what you're saying?
- 你能...  - 我绝对不会这样对他的
- Can you-- - I am not doing that to him.
绝对不会
I am not gonna do that to him.
可现实就是如此
It's a situation that we're in now.
我们去找个私立学校
We'll find a private school.
我们去找个解决的办法
We'll find some sort of way--
乔  就靠你的薪水
Joel, we can't afford a private school
我们负担不起私立学校
on just your salary.
- 什么  - 我是就事论事
- What? - I'm being practical.
看看我们的选择  这不是一个可行的选择
Let's look at our options.That's not an option.
- 靠我的薪水   - 靠你的薪水
- On my salary? - On your salary.
没人让你辞掉工作  不是吗
Well,no one asked you to go quit your job,did they?
但你还是那样做了
But you went and did that.
就跟你跑去跟明基朵老师谈一样
Just like you went and talked to miss Mikindoe.
你所做的所有决定
All these decisions you're making,
都是些不好的决定
they're bad decisions.
你根本就是在帮倒忙
You're not helping, here.
?滚...出我的草坪
? G-get of my lawn
?滚...滚...滚出我的草坪
? g-g-get off my lawn
?什么
? what
?滚...滚...滚出我的草坪
? g-g-get off my lawn
?g-g-get off my lawn
这是首不错的单曲
That's a good single.
你应该在整张专辑出炉之前
You should drop that single first
把这个加进去做第一首单曲
before your whole album comes out.
我觉得这不可能
I was afraid this was gonna happen.
都是什么采访啊
What an interview.
我是说“采访”
I mean "interview."
我都快忘了你走那个家伙的时候
I forgot what a tough guy you are
是有多男人了
that you punched that guy out.
而且他们混音的时候
And then the way they remixed,they really captured
他们真的捕捉到你声音中甜蜜的那一点了
this sweet spot of your voice.
你现在听自娱自乐的对吧
You're pretty happy with yourself right now,aren't you?
说实话  这真让我挺开心的
Honestly,it really picked me up.
- 啊哈  - 确实是
- Uh-huh. - It did.
听着  我在家也挺不顺心的
Look,things aren't perfect for me at home either.
乔巴选了芭蕾做他的冬季运动  而不是篮球
Jabbar chose,over basketball,for his winter sport,ballet.
- 那甚至都不算一项运动  - 挺酷的嘛
- That's not even a sport.Ballet.- That's cool.
- 酷吗  - 对
- It's cool? - Yeah.
- 芭蕾吗  - 有什么问题吗
- Ballet? - What's the problem?
他在家里挺重要的
Well, he was in the outfit.
他拥有整个... 你知道的
He had the whole--you know, he was...
就在那个消除房瞎打转
twirling around the kitchen in a super thin, you know...
- 你看到非常不好受吗  - 而我...就给他打下手
- Is it tough--kind of tough for you to see that?
- And I am ...hands.
- 是吗   - 对
- Yeah? -  Yeah.
班里还有其他男生吗
Is there any other guys in the class?
- 没有  - 看看那个
- No. - Well, look at that.
看看  他在让男女比例协调呢
Look at that.He's working the ratio, there.
班上就他跟一帮女生呢
It's just a bunch of girls and him.
- 他成功的几率很大呢  - 好吧 我...
- He's got it made. - Okay, I-
我才不关心我那才十岁的儿子
I'm not concerned about whether or not
能不能谈到恋爱呢
my 10-year-old's gonna get laid.
我在谈我能跟他分享
I'm talking about being able to share something with him
能跟他一起做的事儿
that I could connect with him on.
我懂了  好吗
I get it, okay?
克罗斯比  你的孩子不会
Crosby,your kids aren't always gonna be interested
总对你感兴趣的东西感兴趣
in the things that you're interested in.
他们也不会总如你所愿
They're not always gonna be interested
成为你想让他们成为的人
in the things you want them to be,okay?
我也希望麦克斯能对篮球
I wish that Max had been more interested
比对虫子感兴趣一点儿
in baseball than bugs.
但这不是我能掌控得了的
That's not how it worked out.
好吗  所以我也对虫子感起了兴趣
Okay? So I got interested in bugs.
嗯哼
Mmhmm.
嘿  小鬼  维克多呢
Hey, bud, where's Victor?
他去外边玩去了
Uh, he's outside playing.
他说天做完作业了
He said he finished his homework.
哦
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
那你呢
How about you?
你选好你要做的任务了吗
Have you chosen which mission you're gonna do?
选好了  圣胡安・卡皮斯特拉诺
Yeah, the San Juan capistrano.
你知道每年有多少燕子飞往那里吗
You know the swallows fly there every year?
我知道诶
I did know that.
你外公外婆在我小的时候
Grandma and grandpa took me down there
带我去过哪儿
when I was a kid.
非常酷的
Pretty cool.
好吧
Okay.
- 妈咪  - 什么事
- Mommy? - Yeah?
要是维克多留级到四年级了
If Victor goes back to fourth grade,
他得做另外一份任务报告吗
will he had to do another missions report?
不会
No.
不会  他做过了
No, he did that.
所以...
So...
天呐  我不...
Gosh, I don't--um...
我不知道
I don't know.
你没跟他说这事对吧
Hey,you haven't talked to him about that,have you?
- 我没有  - 很好
- No, I haven't. - Good.
因为我们现在还没决定好
Because nothing's been decided yet, so...
这件事儿非常复杂  你知道吗
It's just--it's complicated, you know?
对所有成年人来说都是
It's for all the grown-ups.
得要学校跟维克多的老师
It's for the school and for Victor's teachers
还有我跟你爸爸一起解决
and for daddy and I to figure out.
好吗
Okay?
- 好吧  - 好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
这就是你昨天跟老爸吵架吵得那么晚的原因吗
Is that why you and daddy have been fighting so much lately?
没有  我们才没有吵架呢
No, we haven't been fighting.
没有  宝贝
No, sweetie, um, you know,
只是有时候有些分歧而已
sometimes we just disagree,
但都没事了
but that's--that's okay.
我们讨论...
And we discuss things and...
你好  米勒先生
Hello, Mr. Miller.
对  我是克里斯蒂娜・布雷弗曼竞选团队
Yes, this is Adam Braverman calling
的亚当・布雷弗曼
from the Kristina Braverman campaign.
对  我们想问一下你
Yes, we're calling to ask you if you'd be willing
愿意为了让竞选更具竞争性进行
to make a second donation to help
第二次赞助吗
keep this campaign competitive.
- 至少500美元  - 500美元就行
- Minimum of $500. - $500 would be great.
但是我们还可以要高点儿
But we could go higher.
但要是你赞助1000美元就再好不过了
But $1,000 would be even better.
他负担得起的
He can afford it.
非常感谢  谢谢 米勒医生
Thank you very much. Thank you, Dr. Miller.
好吧  谢谢  对  很好  好的
Okay, thank you, yeah.Good, okay.
- 没问题  - 不好意思
- You got it. - Excuse me.
- 嘿  - 你们看过这个了吗
- Hey. - You guys seen this?
- 什么  - 谢谢
- What? - Thank you.
这是什么
What is it?
你们看过这个吗
Have you seen this?
- 这是什么  - 那是什么
- What's this? - What is that?
我看起来太糟了
I look horrible.
你们简直是疯了
You guys look insane.
你们在吼谁呢
Who are you yelling at?
那么看起来跟个疯子似的
You look like lunatics.
海蒂足球比赛的脸书首页
Haddie's soccer Facebook page.
- 这就是那时候的照片  - 这是场足球赛吗
- That's where that's from. - This was a soccer game?
他从网上弄下来的
He took it from the Internet.
裁判员判她失误
The ref called her for tripping.
她正在带球过人
She was making a play on the ball.
我简直不敢相信  他怎么能截下这么一张图
I can't believe--how can he just grab this stuff
还把它放到报纸上呢
and have it be in the paper?
- 因为他是个混蛋  - 这就是他的伎俩
- Because he's a jerk.- That's how he could od this.
我们得召开记者招待会
We need to call a press conference.
- 我觉得我必须这么做了  - 你应该这么做
- I feel that's what I have to do.
- You should call press conference.
我会召开的
I think I'm going to.
- 我们需要召开...  - 很好  是时候了
- We need to call--  - Good.About timee.
那你们要在记者招待会上说什么
And say what in this press conference?
- 是时候什么了  亚当  - 是时候该她反击了
- About time what, Adam?- That she fights back.
- 用什么  - 什么也没有
- With what? - Nothing.
就让他住手
Just tell him to stop it.
你们有事瞒着我
You're not telling me something.
克里斯蒂娜  你是不是手上有那家伙什么把柄
Kristina, you got something on this guy?
我喜欢这个  你喜欢吗
I liked it.Did you like it?
- 我觉得还不错诶  - 嗯哼
- I thought it was good. - Mmhmm.
对  很好
Yeah, it was good.
这是什么
What's this?
- 什么  - 你为什么把它转过来戴
- What? - Why you twiddling it?
- 我不知道啦 - 太大了吗
- I don't know. - Is it too big.
- 不是  - 那我们重新打一下尺寸
- No. - Let's get it resized.
不不不  不是那个原因
No, no, no, it's not that.It's not.
没关系的  他们说我可以把它送回去的
It really doesn't matter.They said I could bring it back.
- 不是那个原因  - 确实太大了
- It's not that. - It is too big.
- 我有个主意  - 什么主意
- I had an idea. - What?
我觉得我们可以一起讨论
I thought we could talk about it together.
- 好吧  - 嗯...
- Okay. - Um...
我一直停不住去想这戒指有多贵
I can't--I can't stop thinking about how much money it was.
- 你能不去想吗  - 太贵重了
- Will you stop? - It was so much.
- 这可是花了你所有的退伍津贴  - 你能别说了吗
- It was all of your combat pay. - Will you stop?
我想让你拥有它  你值得拥有
I want you to have it.You're worth it.
这就是我想把钱花在的地方
This is what I wanted to spend my money on.
这是件特别的事儿
This is a special thing.
但是  宝贝  这正是我在跟你说的
But, baby, that's what I'm saying.
这并不是我不喜欢这段感情
And it's not that I don't love that sentiment,
正是因为我太爱了  但这似乎
because I do, but it's kind of like
就是我们的所有家当了  所以我...
it's our money now,and so I--
我想讨论出最好的花钱方式
I wanted to talk about what the best way to spend it is
因为万一我们想去旅游呢
because, like, what if we want to travel?
要是我们想...
What if we want to...
要是我们想组建一个家庭买套房子呢
What if we want to start a family or get a house?
难道我们...
Like, don't we--
这些都会有的
well, then...All those things are gonna come.
我们不可能一口就吃个大胖子
We're not gonna get them all at once.
但这个戒指将会是你
But this is something that you're gonna have
接下来生活的每一天
for the rest of your life and you're gonna wear
都要戴在身上的
on your finger every single day.
我想让你感到特别
And I want you to feel special and I don't want you to have
我不想让你戴一枚廉价的戒指
some cheap ring that's not gonna--
但是  宝贝  要是我们买一枚更小
but, baby, I would feel just as special
的戒指我一样会感觉很特别
and love something a little smaller just as much
而且我们还能省下钱来
if it felt like we wanted to maybe save
去做别的事儿
some of that money for something else.
这就是我想征求你的意见的事儿
That's all I wanted to get your opinion on.
我... 好吧  好吧
I, uh--yeah, yeah.
我们把它还回去换一枚...
We'll bring it back and trade it in and--
等等  宝贝  你还好吗
well, wait, babe,I wanted--do you feel good?
我是说  这让你觉得有意义吗
I mean, does that make you sense?
你想省点钱去做别的事儿吗
Do you want to save some of that money for something else?
当然  肯定很有意义
Yeah.It makes perfect sense.
- 没什么大不了的  - 瑞恩  你生气了吗
- It's no big deal. - Ryan, are you upset?
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you. - No. I love you too.
这没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
你要吃水果圈了还兴奋吗
Are you excited to eat fruit loops?
你在数着日子
Are you counting down the days
看你什么时候能吃水果圈吗
so that you can eat fruit loops?
- 早上好  亲爱的  - 早上好
- Good morning, my love.- Good morning.
嗨
Hi.
哇哦  你看起来心情很好嘛
Wow, you look like you're in a good mood.
是的  我心情很好
I am. I am.
我非常喜欢跟乔巴一块儿上课
I just love these classes with jabbar.
我是说  我只是不想惹你不高兴
I mean, I'm trying not to jinx it, you know?
但他好像真的爱上了芭蕾
But it seems like he's really into it.
我们之间肯定有什么特殊的联系
You know--you know,we might have something.
对  感觉家里好像有了个小巴雷什尼科夫
Yeah, like a little baryshnikov on our hands.
对  小巴雷什尼科夫
Yeah, a little baryshnikov.
怎么啦  难道这样说不好吗
What?Isn't that a good one?
这样说是很好啦
That's a great one,
但我知道你其实并不喜欢这样  所以...
but I know you're not really cool with it, so...
不不不 我才没有不高兴呢
No, no, I'm not not cool with it.
- 真的吗  - 对
- Really? - Yeah.
我是说  我...
I mean, I'm...
我不是在说我希望他
It wouldn't have been,say,my dream pick
去学芭蕾  而不是去骑肌肉车
that he was into ballet over, say,
摩托车什么的
muscle cars and motorcycles,
但是  你知道的  我不...
but, you know, I'm not,like, hung up
会对男子气概子类的事儿而不安
on the masculinity of it all or anything.
- 好吧  - 嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
很好  因为你根本不必担心
Good, 'cause you really don't need to worry.
他还是你的儿子
He's still gonna be your boy.
你非常男子气概的儿子  好吗
Your very boyish boy, okay?
好吧  你为什么一直粘着我
Okay, why are you getting sticky with me?
- 我才没有一直粘着你呢  - 快点  老妈
- I'm not sticky with you.- Come on, mom.
- 走啦  - 好吧  好吧  好吧
- Let's go. - Okay, okay, okay, okay.
拜  艾达
Bye, aida.
- 跟你哥哥说再见  - 再见  老爸
- Say bye to your brother. - Bye, daddy.
祝你跳芭蕾愉快
Hey, have fun at ballet.
- 好吧  - 下蹲努力点
- Okay. - Plie hard.
踢高一点
And kick high.
- 爱你哟  - 但得先做好准备运动
- Love you. - Limber up first.
快点  老妈  走了
Come on, mom.Let's go.
你为什么不一起来看看我们班呢
Why don't you come check out a class?
我觉得你会喜欢的
I think you'll really like it.
我会考虑得
I will think about that.
我可不想打扰你们之间的事儿
I mean, I don't want to step on your guys' thing.
我可不想把你的感觉给弄没了
You know, I don't want to take that away from you.
- 好吧  - 嘿  哇哦  怎么了
- Okay. - Hey, whoa.What's that?Whoa.
很好  祝你开心
Fine.Have a good day.
我赢不了的
I can't win.
你呢
How about you?
你想上网看球赛吗
You want to watch a little NFL network?
哈
Huh?
我们能一兄弟相称吗  我们能一起撞胸吗
Can we bro out?Can you chest bump?
你能撞胸吗  我们来看看吧
Can you chest bump?Let's see.
真是个好撞胸呢  过来
Oh, that's a great chest bump.Come here.
走去看一小会儿橄榄球
Let's go watch a little football.
就你跟我
You and me.
巧克力薄片煎饼  多加一份巧克力
Chocolate chip pancakes,extra chocolate chips.
好了  我得走了
Okay, I got to run.
但是 老爸  你不能走
But, dad, you can't go.
- 今天可是周六  - 对  我知道 宝贝
- It's Saturday. - Yeah, I know, sweetie.
我今天尽量早点下班
I'll try to keep it short today,okay?
我给你做了鸡蛋  你想吃点什么吗
I was gonna make you eggs.Do you want anything to eat?
不用了  我在路边摊买点吃吧
Uh, no, I'll just eat on site.
- 谢了  - 好吧
- Thanks. - Okay.
马上回来
Be right back.
- 乔  - 什么事
- Joel. - Yeah?
孩子们知道这事儿了
The kids are picking up on this.
知道什么了
On what?
我们俩之间的紧张感  或者他们...
On the tension between us,or they--
那他们肯定不是从我这儿得知的
Well, they're not getting it from me.
乔  昨天西德妮问我
Joel, Sydney asked me yesterday
为什么我们要吵的那么厉害
why we're fighting so much.
我想我们得做得更好了吧
Well,we'll just have to do a better job,I guess.
我们必须得讨论维克多的事儿
We have to talk to Victor and we have to,you know,
我们必须达成一致
get on the same page, here.
- 我们不能一直这样下去  - 我知道  茱莉亚
- We can't be doing this.- I know, Julia.
不能再这样互相斗下去了
Undermining each other,you know?
我会一直支持我的儿子的
I will be there for my son.
从左侧突破了一个巨大的缺口
Powering through a big hole in the left side,
现在已经接近了二十五号
now near the 25.
我搞不懂了  老爸
I don't get it, dad.
这不是我们一小时之前看的
This is not the same game
那场比赛吗
we were watching an hour ago?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
- 你想说什么  - 这个都放了一天了
- What's your point? - They play all day.
他们看起来就像同一组人
These look like the same guys.
- 嗯  - 同样的颜色
- Yeah.- Like, the same colors.
我真不敢相信你就是
I just can't believe that this is how
想这样过周六的
you want to spend your Saturday.
这是你这样过的周六
Well, this is how you're spending your Saturday.
我就不明白了
I mean, I don't understand that.
你应该出去见新朋友的
You should be out there meeting people.
玩啊之类的  你为什么不去
You know, having fun.Why aren't you doing that?
不好意思  我才不需要出去见新朋友呢
Excuse me,I don't need to be out there meeting people.
我在这儿陪我最爱的老爸
I'm here with my dear old dad.
如果你想知道的话
And if you must know,I was invited
我被人邀请去一个派对  但是我不去
to a party tonight,and I'm not going.
你为什么不去
Why aren't you going?
因为  要陪你呀
Because.Here with you.
再加上我什么人都不认识
Plus, I won't...You know, I don't know anybody.
你要是一直坐在这儿陪一个老男人
Well,you're not gonna get a chance to know anybody
你永远都没机会认识任何人
sitting around here with your old man.
我不需要男人  老爸
I don't need a man, dad.
我一个人照样活得好好的
I am fine on my own, you know.
我又不是在说男人  萨拉
Well,I wasn't necessarily talking about a man,Sarah.
- 哦  - 你已经变了  而我...
- Oh. - You've changed, and I...
你开始了一段新的人生
You started this whole new life.
有了个新地方住着
You got a whole new place.
你可以继续出去冒险
You can go out there and have adventures,
你可以像向你母亲说的那样
and you can expand your horizons like your mother's
开阔你的视野
talking about doing.
尽管去做就是了
Just go do that, you know?
那谁来陪你呢
Who's gonna hang out here with you?
真奇怪诶  有你在这儿
Well,quite frankly,having you around here
抱怨我做的事  还...
complaining about what I'm doing, and...
好吧  老爸  我要去开阔我的视野了 好吗
All right, dad,I'm gonna expand, okay?
我要去冒险了
I'm gonna expand my horizons to have an adventure
我马上就去参加派对
and I'm gonna go to this party
尽管我一个人都不认识  好吗
where I don't know anybody, okay?
你这样做一段时间
And while you're doing all of that,
你就会遇到个好男人
you might meet a nice guy.
我不想遇到一个什么男人  老爸
I don't want to met a guy, dad.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Fine.
但为了预防此事发生  我要拿走你的啤酒
But in case I do,I'm taking your beer.
- 晚安   - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
两年前  小鲍跟我的侄女
Two years ago, Bob little had an inappropriate relationship
当时还只是一个十九岁的实习生发生了不正当的关系
with my niece, who was then his 19-year-old assistant.
我不知道我是否该这样做
I don't know if I can do this.
当然  你可以的  克里斯蒂娜
Yes, you can, Kristina.
安博希望你这样做
Amber wants you to.
大家下午好
Good afternoon.
很感谢你们得到来
Thank you all for being here today.
你们其中很多人在我发表
There's a lot more of you here
参选演说的时候也来过
than when I announced my candidacy,
所以很高兴再次见到你们
so it's good to see.
我不认为一个竞选应该
I don't think this campaign
掺杂个人攻击
should be about personal attacks,
所以 在经过自我反省之后
which is why after much soul-searching,
我被迫得毫无顾忌的向媒体说出
I am compelled to speak out against what's been going on
关于我的家人  我自己的一些真相
in the media, about my family,about myself.
三年前  当我丈夫在杂货店的时候
Three years ago,my husband was checking out
一个非常无力的人
of a grocery store when a very rude man
叫我儿子拖油瓶
called my son a retard.
既然我们都觉得”拖油瓶“
And while I think we can all agree
这个词非常丑陋不堪
that the word "retard"is very ugly,
要是换做你们的儿子患了艾斯伯格综合症的话
I think it's really offensive when your son
你们也会觉得被冒犯
has Asperger's syndrome.
所以  我的丈夫  作为一个想保护
So my husband,being the protective father
自己儿子的男人  他...
that he is...
就走了那个人
Well, he punched the man.
事实上  我之所以竞选市长
Actually,one of the reasons why I'm running for mayor
的其中一个原因就是要反抗
and one of the things that I'm fighting against
此类歧视的事儿
is exactly this type of intolerance.
我丈夫当时不会容忍  我也不会
My husband won't stand for it,and neither will I.
或许你们会说这只是我们的价值观
I guess you could say that those are our values.
所以要是你们还有疑问的话
So if you have any questions,
我也很乐意回答
I'd be happy to answer.
你认为小鲍在此次竞选当中
What do you think about Bob little's tactics
使用了什么策略
in this campaign?
此时我不做评论
I have no comment.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
都这么晚了
It's so late.
我都给你打了好几次电话了
I tried to call you a couple times.
抱歉  我不知道  抱歉
Sorry. I don't know.Sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
下班太晚了
Got off late.
我把戒指还回去了
I took the ring back.
轻而易举
Pretty easy.
- 是吗   - 对
- You did? - Yeah.
还是管用的
So it's all gonna work out.
你感觉如何
Um, how do you feel?
你觉得还好吗  能接受吗
Do you feel...Do you feel okay about it all?
当然  感觉非常好
Yeah, yeah.I feel great.
我们再去买个更合适的就行
Just gonna get the right one.
因为你知道并不是
'Cause you know-- you know it's not
因为我不够爱它
that I didn't love it very much.
- 我很爱它   - 我知道
- I did. - No, I know.
因为这样对我们更好一些  对吗
It's because it's better for us, right?
- 这样我们...  - 绝对的
- Like, we can--  - Absolutely. Yeah.
- 真的吗  - 真的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我是真想这么做
I really want to do that.
- 好吧  - 这样非常好
- Okay. - That's good.
- 很好  - 对
- Good. - Yeah.
你想让我过来陪你一会儿吗
Hey,you want a little company over there?
我马上就上床来
Ah, I'm gonna come to bed in just a sec.
我就想先放松会儿
I'm just--I'm just relaxing.
嗯
Mm.
嘿  小鬼  我们能谈谈吗
Hey, kiddo.Can we talk?
当然
Sure.
好吧
Okay.
嗯...
Um...
这周我跟你爸
This week, your dad and I
跟明基朵老师谈过了
have been talking to miss Mikindoe.
- 我惹什么麻烦了吗  - 没有
- Am I in trouble? - No.
- 刚好相反  - 对  一点麻烦也没有
- No, just the opposite. - Yeah, not at all.
我们很为你骄傲
So proud of you, man.
大家都知道你学习很努力
Everybody knows you're working so hard.
我的成绩还是很差
My grades still suck.
我们想让你
Well, here's what we want for you.
换个地方学习
We want you to have a place
好让你能跟上进度
where you can take some time to catch up
你也能有更多的时间提升你的阅读能力
and you can work on your reading skills.
而且我跟你爸觉得
And so your dad and I thought that it would be
让你在下半年去四年级念书对你有好处
good for you to spend the rest of the year in fourth grade.
我不想...我不想这么做
I don't want to--I don't want to do that.
我能理解
I can understand that.
我们会一直陪着你的
And we'll be here for you the whole time.
不不  这不公平
No, no, this isn't fair.
我们这学年都过了快一半了
We're almost half way through the year.
儿子  我知道这很不公平
Buddy, I know it doesn't seem fair.
我们可能会尽快这么做  维克多
We probably should have done it sooner,Victor,
但我们想知道这是不是正确的决定
but we want to make sure it was the right decision.
但是我会跟西德妮在同一个年级
But then I'll be in the same grade as Sydney?
那我的朋友怎么办
And what about all my friends?
我就在也见不着他们了
I'll never see them again.
你还记得你才来的时候吗
You remember when you started little league?
你还记得当时有多难
Do you remember how hard that was
你一开始有多害怕吗
and how scary it was to you at first?
你从没放弃
You'd never done it.
- 而且你那么努力  - 没错
- And you practiced so hard. - Exactly.
你花了时间
You really put in the time.
你也花了不少努力  后来不是变好了吗
You put in the work and then it clicked for it.
现在也会那样的
And that's what this is gonna be.
你会回到四年级  你会
You're gonna go back to fourth and you're gonna,you know,
继续努力  然后事情一样会顺利的
try so hard and then it's just gonna click.
你知道吗  会好起来的
You know?It's just gonna click for you.
- 从那儿开始...  - 维克多
- And from that point on...- Victor.
你做得到的
You can do this.
你是个勇敢的男孩  你做得到的
You're a brave boy.I know you can do this
我么也会一直帮你的
and we'll help you.
会好起来的  儿子
It's gonna be fine.Buddy.
我想一个人待会儿
I want to be left alone.
出去
Get out.
我说了  出去
I said to get out!
行了
Yeah.
哇哦
Wow.
- 嗨  - 嗨  亲爱的
- Hi! - Hi, sweetie.
米莉
Millie!
我正要出去呢  你就打给我了
You just caught me on my way out.
我正准备去赶汽车呢
I was about to run for the bus.
好吧  天呐
Okay.Boy.
嘿  米尔  卡米尔  你看起来真漂亮  亲爱的
Hey, mill--Camille,you look beautiful, honey.
你玩的开心吗
Are you having a great time?
太棒了
Oh, it's just been amazing.
让我看看  从哪儿说起呢
Um, let me see.Where do I start?
我们每天早上都在作画
We've been painting every morning.
老师真是太优秀了
The teacher is just--he's just extraordinary.
- 我受益颇多   - 这就好
- I'm learning so much. - Oh, good.
明天我们要去佛罗伦萨
And tomorrow we go to Florence.
我们要素描乌菲齐
We're going to sketch at the uffizi.
- 什么  - 乌菲齐
- What? - The uffizi.
是一个博物馆
The--it's a museum.
哦  很好  太棒了
Oh, great, great, great.
这就是说你玩的很开心咯
Well,I mean,so you're really enjoying yourself?
哦 哇哦
Oh, wow.
还有食物
And the food.
亲爱的  我们简直爱死它了
Sweetie, you would jut love it.
意大利面真是太新鲜了
The pasta is so fresh!
不管你在哪儿吃都是那么嚼劲十足
It's always Al dente.It doesn't matter where you eat.
即使是在一个很简陋的小餐馆都是一样
Could be a little hole-in-the-wall restaurant.
我很开心你玩的那么高兴
Well, I'm glad you're having a good time.
- 你呢  - 很好
- How are you? - Great.
很好 很好  一切都还好
Great, great.Everything's fine here.
我浇着那些植物  孩子们也是不是过来看看
I'm watering the plants.The kids are stopping by.
他们烦死我了  但是
They're bothering me,but, you know,
我想你了  米莉
I miss you, Millie.
我想你了
I miss you.
- Andiamo  - 我得走了
- Andiamo. - Oh, I gotta go.
这是车要开了的意思
That means the bus is leaving.
但是...好吧  别错过汽车了
But...okay, well,don't miss your bus.
米莉  我爱你
Millie, I love you.
你...我爱你
Did you--I love you!
但是...
But...
怎么...
What...
好吧
Okay.
亲爱的  这其实也算件好事儿
Honey, it's actually kind of good.
大家都挺积极的回应着这件事
People are responding in a really positive way.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yup.
“我们一直挺你  克里斯蒂娜  继续斗争下去
"We're with you, Kristina.Keep up the good fight.
站在你自己家人那边”
Way to stand up for your family."
看看
Look at that.
所以他们也会做同样的事儿
So they would have done the same thing.
看吧  你不诽谤别人也同样
See,you don't need to participate in
能赢得竞赛
a smear campaign to win this thing.
这不是我们要做的 对吗
That's not what we're about,right?
这不是你要做的
It's not what you're about.
你也一样
You either.
你做出的选择
Well, you made the choice.
无论发生了什么  我都为你而骄傲
And no matter what happens,I'm proud of you for that.
你坚持了自我
You stuck to your guns.
你没有使阴招
You didn't go for the jugular
即使我跟海瑟都告诉你该这样做
even though Heather and I were both telling you to do that.
- 你做了正确的事儿  - 你们也是在帮我  谢了
- You did the right thing.- You guys trying to help.Thanks.
我才不只这样说呢
I'm not just saying all this
因为你让我看起来跟个卑鄙小人一样
'cause you made me look like a badass.
你确实是个卑鄙小人
You are a badass.
- 我不是  克里斯蒂娜  - 你就是
- I'm not a badass, Kristina.- You're a badass.
我不是  我只是个男人而已  好吗
I'm not.I'm just a man, okay?
有时候一个男人应该在某人
Sometimes a man needs to kick a little ass
需要被踢的时候踢他一脚
when somebody's ass needs kicking.
- 没错  - 好吧
- That's correct. - Okay.
- 你是个好父亲   -谢谢  我爱你
- And you are a good dad.- Thank you. I love you.
- 也是最好的丈夫   - 我爱你
- And the best husband. - I love you.
天呐  她吓到我了
Gosh.She scares me.
她有好事儿的时候从不发短信的
She never texts when it's good--
你为什么不告诉她你需要十五分钟呢
why don't you just tell her you need 15 minutes.
怎么啦
What is it?
降了四个百分点
Dropped four points.
嗯...
Um...
好吧
Okay.
- 被拉至六个百分点了  - 没关系的
- Training by six.- That's okay.
你告诉过我这些事儿
You told me that these things
会有错误的余地的  对吗
have a margin of error, right?
那么两分  你可以被落后
By a couple points,so you could have just dropped
一两分的  只是有一点波动而已
a point or two,and that could just be a little fluctuation.
根本不关记者招待会什么事
Doesn't have to necessarily do with the press conference.
对
Right.
克里斯蒂娜  你会赢的
Kristina,you can win this thing.
对
Right.
不好意思
Excuse me.
来了
Coming.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
你现在不是我的房东
You're not my super.
- 快进来  - 谢了
- Come in. - Thanks.
很高兴你来了
So glad you're here.
- 你看起来很漂亮  - 谢谢
- You look beautiful. - Thank you.
我能请你喝一杯吗
Can I get you a drink?
可以  当然  等会儿吧
Um, yes, sure, in a minute.
- 好吧  - 我不知道啦
- Okay. - I don't know.
快过来  见见他们
Come on in.Meet some people.
阿历克斯  我能打断你一下吗
Uh, Alex, can I interrupt you?
哦  不好意思  当然  嗨
Oh, excuse me.Yes, hi.
阿历克斯・沙曼  来见见萨拉・布雷弗曼
Alex samson,meet Sarah Braverman.
- 嗨  - 很高兴见到你
- Hi.- Nice to meet you.
萨拉是一位很优秀的摄影师
Sarah is a really talented photographer.
哪种摄影师
Oh, what kind of photography?
- 就猫狗之类宠物的  - 你知道吗
- Uh, dogs and cats. - You know what?
我们曾经开了一个韦格曼术展  真是非常棒
We once had a wegman exhibit. It was fantastic.
- 那真是太棒了  - 我也去看过
- That was great. - I saw that too.
- 嗯  啊哈   - 哇哦
- Yes, huh-huh. - Wow.
谢谢观看  更多字幕请关注“幕雨字幕组”新浪微博